collive.com 2019-11-03

# Privacy Policy - COLlive

collive.com (“the Site”) respects the privacy of our users and members. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information that we collect and the uses that we make of that information. we provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by or services and which includes any online or mobile websites or digital services owned, operated or offered by, on behalf of, or in conjunction our services, including any online or mobile website, application or digital service installation through which this Privacy Policy appears (each a “Service,” collectively the “Services”). “Users” are persons that use the Services.  
We wish to protect every users privacy. If you are an EU citizen please read this policy carefully and use our site and services only if you agree to all terms and to the collection and use of private information.  
Information We Collect:  
The Site gathers personal and general demographic information about users who provide said information willingly during registration as members to our site. When registering on this site, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail address, zip code, country and other demographic information. We receive both information that is directly provided to us, such as personal information you provide when you visit the Services, and information that is passively or automatically collected from you, such as anonymous information collected from your browser or device. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to all of this as the “Information”.  
We, and 3rd parties who include (but not limited to: third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and distribution or other partners may use automated means to collect various types of Information about you, your computer or other device used to access our Services. types of automatically collected information may include (but not limited to): network or Internet protocol address (IP address) and type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Safari, Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, mobile network, device identifiers (such as an Apple IDFA or an Android Advertising ID), device settings, browser settings, the web pages of the Services you have visited, Services visited before and after you visit a Service Geo location information, and the content and advertisements you have accessed, seen, forwarded and/or clicked on.  
You may with our content, on or through social media services or other third party platforms, such as Facebook, or other third-party social media plug-ins, integrations and applications. When you engage with our content on or through social media services or other third party platforms, plug-ins, integrations or applications, you may allow us to have access to certain Information in your profile. This may include your name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, an ID associated with the applicable third party platform or social media account user files, like photos and videos, your list of friends or connections, people you follow and/or who follow you, or your posts or “likes.” For a description on how social media services and other third party platforms, plug-ins, integrations or applications handle your information, please refer to their respective privacy policies and terms of use, which may permit you to modify your privacy settings.  
Use Of Your Information:  
We may use your personal identifying information in a number of ways related to your use of our site. We may, from time to time, use your personal identifying information in connection with sending you specific, targeted information or advertising that may be of interest to you. We may use your contact information, such as your e-mail address, to send you our newsletter and periodic special promotions.  
Some examples of use of data include (but are not limited to)  
provide and communicate with you about the Services or your account with us,  
fulfill your requests regarding the Services, including without limitation requests for newsletters and notifications,  
respond to your inquiries, and notify you if you have won a contest,  
communicate with you about other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you,  
enforce the legal terms (including without limitation our policies and terms of service) that govern your use of our Services, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the Information,  
provide technical support for the Services,  
prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities (including, without limitation, copyright infringement) on or through the Services,  
protect the safety of our Users,  
customize or personalize ads, offers and content made available to you based on your visits to and/or usage of the Services or other online or mobile websites, applications, platforms or services, and analyze the performance of those ads, offers and content, as well as your interaction with them,  
perform analysis regarding how you use the Services or any part thereof,  
We may use any information you provide in order to investigate, or assist any authority in investigating, suspicion of illegal activity or acts on the collive website or on any of the site’s services.  
Promotions and contests that run on The Site may be sponsored, in whole or in part, by companies other than The Site. Data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor.  
As a registered user, you may opt out of receiving emails and special offers, promotions or mailings at any time. Only those registered users who have not opted out of receiving such communications will receive such emails. We may transfer some or all of your Information if we, or one of our business units, undergoes a business transition, like a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or part of our assets  
Cookies:  
We make use of “cookies,” which are small sets of information stored onto your computer in connection with your use of our web site. We use cookies to store temporary individual user information concerning your use of this site and your user identification. We may also use information gathered by cookies for editorial purposes, marketing and adverting purposes, to measure certain traffic patterns on our web site or for similar purposes. We do not control and are not responsible for the use of cookies or other identifiers by anyone except our site.  
Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies. You may be able to set your browser to warn you before accepting certain cookies or to refuse certain cookies. However, if you disable the use of cookies in your web browser, some features of the Services may be difficult to use or inoperable.  
Disabling Cookies:  
If you wish to disable cookies you may do so through your web browser options. Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites. Alternatively, you may use the resources located at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices to opt out  
We may work third-party companies that use techniques other than HTTP cookies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity, including those integrated with our Services. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these techniques, and those browser settings that block conventional cookies may have no effect on such techniques.  
At this time we may not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include “do not track” instructions  
E-Mail:  
Using the e-mail addresses provided during registrations, surveys, and contests, we may, periodically, send promotional e-mail to our subscribers about services offered by us, and by carefully selected advertisers. If you do not wish to receive solicitations sent on behalf of third parties, you may unsubscribe at any time.  
Access to certain personal Information that is collected by us and that we maintain may be available to you. For example, if you provided us your email and other information, you can access that account to review the Information you provided.  
You may also send an e-mail to ads@collive.com requesting access to or correction of your personal Information.  
Security:  
Although we take precautions against security breaches, hackers pose a threat to any Internet user. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to see that your information is treated in compliance with this privacy policy.  
The Privacy Policy was updated on June 9, 2019
